something took
it something took
it someone that doesn't want to be
here
w
sh
all
right let's do
this got two pills already rigged up
from yesterday's donut
session down at kingscliff New South
Wales but today we're up back up in
py Queensland has had a ban on uh
Spanish for 3
weeks that's why we've been heading down
there but
uh yeah today we're back I expect there
to be quite a few joining us it's a nice
day it's a few
waves but um no really good conditions
otherwise I need to make some new
rigs running low
here this rig is a little bit too
short yeah I need to be better prepped
for next
season I've been without sliming macro
bait
for a long
time good few
weeks and it really makes a difference
in what you're catching I know this that
at least anyway I'm going to get
going hopefully we can find some
mackerel or yesterday at Kings clip
there was a couple of small tuna around
so they're starting to show up
too oh yeah
found myself a sponsor a hack
sponsor there we go but yeah
pen likes my videos and uh decid to give
me a
hat I love their gear as you all know I
use all their gear so but they also sent
me a new Rod so that's what we're trying
today let's see how it goes it's almost
identical to uh what I had previously so
should be all
right have yet to catch a fishing it
though
now we just got to find a fish to
complete this
journey it's looking a little bit dead
on the
Sounder and I
don't hear anyone yelling or drags G
of so I assume it's going to be a little
bit tough to find them
maybe the OD Spanish I
suspect he here we just got to find them
and convince
them something took it something took
it someone that doesn't want to be
here
not sure it's just in by the by the
kayak when it hooked up no idea to me it
look like
a whenever a pike hits the lure in the
surface in Canada or or
Sweden exactly like
that I'll take it
though
I mean could be a shock but I've never
seen a shock take it that Shar out just
like dumb
dogs what could it
be
yep 30 m
left oh
yeah I'm going to roll out tuna because
tuna would still be
gone
M all right now I'm going to say it's
sitting like a Shar
better not
be well we're getting some action at
least it's better than than
nothing it looks
silver definitely looks silver still 15
20 M away
but come
on got me a bit
excited
I need fish my fridge is
empty surviving of uh Frozen stuff at
the
moment we've had pretty big swell on the
gold
coaster so yeah it hasn't been that much
kaying
just don't want to
[Music]
come this is one thing that's awesome
with the kayaks I just just follows the
fish use the kak to Tire them
out as long as they're not pulling you
into
boats or off to New
Zealand
I wish I was filming when this
happened smashed it in the surface like
I had this probably it was only 5 m
away all right we're on red now that's
10 m bit left should be able to see him
a big Spanish
guys big Spanish can you believe that
taking it in the
[Music]
surface
see how he just sitting in the treble
here
I just Gaff the
[Music]
C there we
go oh yeah not
happy can you believe that let took it
in the
surface beautiful
beautiful dust as the ban ended
too that's awesome all right let me
clean this up so yeah Spanish mackerel
king mackerel as you call them over
in
America there you go
whoops
and this is where it was uh stuck it was
just hanging on like that's where the
hook was it's hanging on only
just but
yeah that'll be dinner for the week and
uh Happy
Days I'm
filming rude
planes
so yeah
one
Spanish very nice dinner for the week
finally we've uh we've had three weeks
of surf there been days when you could
fish but I've been a bit lazy to maybe
prioritize surfing a little bit anyway
I'm going to pack up and uh yeah hope
you're having a good day I'll see you
next time peace
out
wait up here a little bit see what we
got before we get into
this
on
I like sitting on the back of a small
one at the end of a
set all
right we're through that Impact Zone and
we just got to get through the shore
break without stuffing
up
same thing
again try to sit on the back of a small
one sometimes I M time this and I just
go
over
kind of as soon as I can I'll Stand
Up